ようこそ! ワルキューレ・ワールドへ
Youkoso! Walküre World e
Welcome! To Walküre World
Google Translate - It's bad.
Kaname Buccaneer, twenty-two!
I'm a former solo idle but battle is OK also
I'm the leader, pulling everyone in the strategy live.
[Nice to meet you!]
Reina Prowler, 15 years old
Jellyfish is only truly distubingly cute and lovely
Hacking rolling stone
Easy Victory!
Any door is open to me!
[Rolling Stone]
[Poisonous!]
Makina Nakajima, 18 years old
Mecha mecha beautiful sexy knife
Fluffy body
Taking care of Rai Rai
Leave it to me!
[Take Care!]
Mikumo Guynemmer, my age is secret!
Unidentified God Demon Death
The strongest diva, Mysterious Venus
[I want to know!]
Freyja Wion, 15 years old
I love apples
I'm the New Face
Riding the wind
My Rune shines when I sing and dance
[It's shiny!]
Music is life!
Music is love!
Music is hope!
Music is mysterious!
Music is energy!
I'll let you know
Goddess song
Super space-time Venus
Walküre!
Our singing voice is invincible.
We go through the galaxy and change the world
Walküre!
I want to sing my feelings
Explosion, creation of heaven and earth
Walküre!
Goddess stage
Change history beyond space-time
Walküre!
I should be able to go more
Golly assault, complete combustion
If you fly, you can fly
Absolutely, If you fly, you can fly
Welcome to Walküre World!
Hear The Universe
Winterbells1 - Macross Wiki
Once you accept this challenge, you’ll be a breakout universal girl!
There are many sounds in this world that you don’t know.
Melodies that you don’t know...
(booting up from shutdown.)
Hiding a useless, mad love
That you can never cry over,
You’re a foolish dancer
(Infusing our five prayers, we’ll sing now!)
Hear the universe!
No one else will explain
The exceptional you living within this story.
Why not get all worked up,
Risking your life in the night?
Blast on through me,
As you please.
Why not take this challenge,
A forceful “hold me tight”?
Do it quickly, before this time runs out for good!
There are many things happening in this world that you don’t know.
Mysteries that no one knows of...
(rotating into motion)
I’m love’s problematic child,
A stimulated purist!
I dance all through the night!
(Infusing our five prayers, we’ll sing now! Ah)
To where you are!
(Infusing our five prayers, we’ll send them to you!)
Ba-dum! Young girls
Live their lives through each heartbeat.
An exceptional dream lives within their story.
That might be a good way to put it!
Hey, pirate radio!
We’ll sing for you with sweet, sweet voices!
We’ll kiss you, one by one!
The formula for pleasure
Is a dreadful, dreadful, dizzying tempest.
We’ll sound out this unhearable music, all the way to where you are!
Why not just explode,
Torn two ways in the night?
I beg your pardon,
Just run on through me!
Why not go on a rampage,
An intoxicated “hold me tight”?
Do it quickly, before this time runs out for good!
[Hurry!]
That might not be a good way to put it…
Celestial music is overflowing
With a dark, dark power to cut through the darkness.
I believe we can resonate with one another, crossing over the deep, deep valleys
To become one.
That might be nice!
Hey, pirate radio!
We’ll sing for you with sweet, sweet voices!
We’ll kiss you, one by one!
The formula for pleasure
Is a dreadful, dreadful, dizzying tempest.
We’ll sound out this unhearable music, all the way to where you are!
Why not get all worked up,
Risking your life in the night?
Blast on through me, as you please.
Why not take this challenge,
A forceful “hold me tight”?
Do it quickly, before this time runs out for good!
MC1
不確定性COSMIC☆MOVEMENT
Fukakuteisei☆COSMIC MOVEMENT
Uncertain☆COSMIC MOVEMENT
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
Even if it breaks the laws of this universe,
I want to keep dancing 'till I die... Ah!
Ride on.
3, 2, 1!
Stars, humans, and apples are all made the same,
Whether it be of spores, quantums, or particles.
Pa Shuwappu Shuwashu YEAH
Even if we're on board with a lawful rhythm,
(Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa Pa)
If we get off course, our fate can change to something unexpected.
How shocking☆
But when we fall in love, we start to feel
The popping of fizz, the rising of wind...
The joining of hands, the flow of our body's heat...
Dance, Dance, join Dance!
Awakening throughout our bodies
Is an Uncertain☆Cosmic☆Movement!
With you, I break through these waves of phrase.
If we fly just one more inch, right・now, we'll be free!
You see? In a moment's kiss,
we'll synchronize with the world:
Boom Boom Boom Boom Space!
Even if we took different shapes and forms,
The world would probably say, "What's the difference? It's all the same!"
How stimulating☆
It's kinda like the feeling of being in love:
The sound of rain, the shape of waves...
The raising of our hands, the increase in our body's heat...
Dance, Dance, join Dance!
Feeling a reaction throughout our bodies,
We see comets transform into musical notes.
A reverberating wind forms a bridge overcoming our distance.
Right ・now, if we fly just one more inch, we'll be in a different world!
You see? At the drop of a tear,
we'll synchronize with the world
Boom Boom, Boom Boom Space!
Are you OK?
Yeah! 3,　2, 1!
Ride on!
Cosmic
It's all overflowing from my body. I feel it might all just evaporate.
Particles of life are seeking you, sparkling brightly!
Not even gravity will hold us down,
In this Uncertain☆Cosmic☆Movement!
With you, I break through these waves of phrase.
Right ・now, if we fly just one more inch, we'll be free!
You see? In a moment's kiss,
we'll synchronize with the world
Boom Boom, Boom Boom Space!
NEO STREAM
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
We never know what the future will bring...
Believe that there's a silver lining.
No need to fear what we should do,
Just to overcome all the difficulties.
In a deep hole of sadness, a secret wanders one morning.
Flowers are drenched in tears, without reason.
Their missions call to one another...
Following your instinct.
Wherever you are, just remember, To look up at the stars.
That breath seeking an answer is a beautiful nobility;
The eternal wish of this blue planet...
... for tomorrow!
Never be satisfied;
Human desires are limitless.
Inside and outside,
There may be complicated emotion.
Desire is relentless...
Whether viewed from front or back,
Ah... it's a critical situation
It's harder to define:
Feel alone, depressed, and hopeless...
Reality and dream get into desperate situation.
The ages battle to and fro;
Reality and dreams,
Ah... in a dire situation!
Now let's blow this flashing, sparking-
There's a burning flame.
Howling sparks... a whirling blaze...
There's a freedom in galaxy,
United in having the space.
At the end I’ll jump on through a whole new world!
Two mysteries meet one another by chance;
Now and then I would wonder...
It's amazing chemistry!
They melt into one,
Their light reaching the sky,
Where a brand new world comes to fruition.
There's a freedom in galaxy,
United in having the space.
At the end I’ll jump on through a whole new world!
Absolute 5
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
Another ray of light gathered amid the overflowing darkness.
Bearing an exhausted voice, it reached the end of its journey.
Following miracle after miracle, melodies rising to the surface were tightly tied -
Strong enough to blow away that black gravity.
Under a borrowed sky, the 5 of us become eternal.
I'm sure that's the only answer we need... so act quickly:
"Why not look to the sky?"
If we're destined to fall apart, at least hold out until this is all over...
So we can deliver this world to those nearly withering hands!
As our sound image begins to break apart, weave it together with these bonds:
Layer upon layer, form a line of defense
Make it the greatest song ever known!
Innocent adults are crying from the pain of a faint memory;
Rather than extending words, we need only look over them, quietly.
The shadows and sadness cast by hope fly by with sidelong glances;
Given this smallest chance, we need only put our fingers to the strings.
If we grow too distant, this radiance will fade;
If our memories will eventually interfere with this warmth... then act quickly:
"Forget already!"
This single string of voices becomes strong enough to ascend...
Take these flower petals bloomed in the 5th dimension and cast them unto tomorrow!
Strip away those emotions, 'cause we're fine just as we are:
Produce volume loud enough to see,
Sounding out again and again!
"It's so loud!"
If even one of us is missing, this meaning will be lost;
All we can do is keep re-affirming this connection.
If we're destined to fall apart, at least hold out until this is all over...
'Cause we can deliver this happily blooming bouquet!
As our sound image begins to dance, let a smile grace your lips:
Resound this song of happiness,
Sending it far enough to fade from sight -
Until this fate is finally changed!
LOVE! THUNDER GLOW
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
SHOULD GO!
MY LOVE! THUNDER GLOW for YOU
RIDE ACROSS THE BLUE
Desire quivers
Depicting a spiral;
It'd be so ridiculous
If my good side only exists in the mirror.
Running from that spark,
I was afraid of breaking apart;
Yeah... I was hiding my fuse all along!
Shuddering on the brink: the water's surface, a dream there!
To make it overflow, I need the proper determination!
The signals are telling me: it's a state of emergency!
For me to become a fallen angel... it almost seems like a lie.
We're twin cosmos
With differing personalities,
Lacking communication;
But if we complete the puzzle, we can let it all roar out!
On a sudden whim, I lied,
Covering it up with kindness...
But I forgot to seal it with a kiss.
Throbbing to the point of breaking: my skin, the sky!
This heart tearing through is like gunpowder.
The time is coming: break the shell!
Lightning will run— when you feel its trembling, jazz out!
Dried mischief... rusting false strength...
With a vibrating gaze, let's turn them into a knife...
To tear away this expressionless face!
I'll turn the key...
On that forgotten lock!
Shuddering on the brink: the water's surface, a dream there!
To make it overflow, I need the proper determination!
The signals are telling me: it's a state of emergency!
For me to become a fallen angel... it seems like a lie.
Throbbing to the point of breaking: my skin, the sky!
This heart tearing through is like gunpowder.
The time is coming: break the shell!
Lightning will run when you feel its trembling, jazz out!
I'll embrace you...
So foolish, our past...
Once it overflows: jazz...
いけないボーダーライン
Ikenai Bōdārain
Ikenai Borderline
Series Subtitles
I fell in love the moment our eyes met
I frantically chased after him
I had a burning desire to know more
The more I searched, the deeper the mystery.
The more I yearned, the hotter I burned
And so the more I dove into that
unknown world (ahh)
Anyone can believe in love or dreams
But it's no fun if you don't chase after them
Love at the limit, the forbidden borderline, No matter the challenge,
I'll break through it all!
Dancing swiftly, pulling even more G's, senses are fading
My body is losing control... I'm gonna fly away!
The friends I used to hang out with,
And that one person I sought
I'll continue to shine until we meet again!
The brighter the light, the darker the shadow,
The stronger the fire, the greater the ash
The faster I run, the clearer it becomes, that dangerous line (ahh)
Freedom and peace will bloom if you wish
But if you hesitate, they'll wither away!
Love at the limit, Dangerously borderless, it's just insane,
Yet I'm still accelerating!
Dancing swiftly, if this is my limit, go ahead and destroy me!
I am made from destruction and rebirth
Love at the limit, the forbidden borderline! No matter the challenge,
I'll break through it all!
Dancing swiftly, pulling even more G's, senses are fading,
My body is losing control... I'm gonna fly away!
Love at the limit, the forbidden borderline, even while my flame burns out,
I'll keep shining bright!
Dancing swiftly, for you, for the future,
No matter how many times I shatter!
By loving,
I am born again.
Since I want to be loved,
I will return alive
MC2
ジリティック <3 BEGINNER
Jiritikku <3 BEGINNER
Giritic <3 BEGINNER
おにゃの子☆girl
Onya no Ko☆Girl
Series Subtitles / Peppermint 2.0 on YouTube
Pounding heart, sideways glance, brand new and
Aching tears (Shine)
Knock on this heart-break door
I want you to
You are my brand new
Aching tears (Shine)
Hug, hug, fluffy, fluffy, dust me in sugar
I want you to
No boys allowed
In girly girl’s dreams
But the kiss we shared
Was a moment sweeter than chocolate
This sigh that feels like it’s about to melt, I’ll sprinkle it on you
Here, take another bite towards the world of love
Pounding heart, sideways glance, brand new and
Aching tears (Shine)
Knock on this heart-break door
I want you to
You are my brand new
Aching tears (Shine)
Hug, hug, fluffy, fluffy, dust me in sugar
I want you to
Bumping against you underneath the table.
You can feel our connection from the tips of our toes. can't you?
I want you to sweep me away at supersonic speed
But you're too nice a person
From the silhouette of two overlapping shadows
Aching tears
Knock on this heart-break door
I want you to
From my heart, hollow like a donut
Aching tears
Hug, hug, fluffy, fluffy, dust me in sugar
I want you to
Your flirtatious glances are brand new, so
Aching tears (Shine)
Knock on this heart-break door
I want you to
You are my brand new
Aching tears (Shine)
Hug, hug, fluffy, fluffy, dust me in sugar
I want you to
Silent Hacker
Series Subtitles / Google Translate
Flashing indications
Hidden back door to my heart
Words that don’t connect
(Don’t connect)
Unknown code
(Unknown code)
Ice cold firewall
(Login completed)
Burning hot anonymous
Unstoppable time
(Unstoppable)
Your voice
(Your voice)
End of the galaxy where the sky is burning
Connect again
You’re not alone
I want to know the real you
Your sad smile
Is an avatar to hide your pain
Thorw it away
Looking back, sadness is always
The moment we exist in
Please don’t forget
I’m here by your side
Silent Hacker
The power to feel
With the fluctuating electronic beach
Unleash someday
Return to your free self
I'm ready to jack inside
I'm gonna jack in hard, jack in deep
Prayer protocol repeat
I want to know the real you
Your sad smile
Is an avatar to hide your pain
Thorw it away
Looking back, sadness is always
The moment we exist in
Please don’t forget
I’m here by your side
Here
Hacking you
Misete
Kimi no
Subete
Hacking you
Kitto
Sugu ni
Yoru wa
Akeru
ワルキューレのバースデイソング
Walküre no Bāsudeisongu
Walküre Birthday Song
God Bless You
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki & Intercosmic Harmony - Youtube
Gently closing my eyes, I hold onto one wish,
Never putting it to words... but surely, I still believe.
I can always feel the up and down of your chest;
I'll never forget this time spent deep in each others' eyes.
Whenever this feeling seems about to spill out, (this feeling)
I suddenly feel like crying... every time. (every time)
Please don't let this piece of destiny slip away...
God Bless You
Having met amid the shining winds,
We'll never lose our way again - our hearts burning with passion, right here and now!
God Bless You
Could you have known this would happen all along? Thank you...
Thank you for those days you spent looking after me!
Your lips are a bit cold when touching mine, but
Every time that happens, I listen to my heart
I wasn't even aware, that my whole being
wanted to be lost in that warm embrace
As I get lost in the crowd (confused)
Mt anxiety builds up (hiding)
Throughout my life, pretending not to notice... until yesterday
God Bless You
I never thought I'd be able to love someone this much -
Now that I know this feeling, I'll never be the same!
God Bless You
We shared the one true happiness that exists in this world:
That's the reason for my joy... and these overwhelming tears!
Even if one single drop (of blue sadness),
Were to fall in your heart... I'll release an arrow of light! (Pierce on through!)
If this love is a miracle... please, God... guide it every step of the way!
Every day, every night, every time, everywhere with you...
God Bless You
I never thought I'd be able to love someone this much -
Now that I know this feeling, I'll never be the same!
God Bless You
Having met amid the shining winds,
We'll never lose our way again - our hearts burning with passion, right here and now!
God Bless You
I wonder if I knew it from the beginning
Thank you for the days when I was always there and watching over me!
Gently closing my eyes, I hold onto one wish,
Never putting it to words... but surely, I still believe.
風は予告なく吹く
Kaze wa yokoku naku fuku
The Wind Blows Without Warning
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
A constellation that comes but once every 30 years is drawing near.
I don't want to sleep - I just want to stay by your side until it passes by.
I can feel my gears ever so slightly turning;
(Can you hear my heart?)
I bet you've never really thought about how many seconds there are, In a year... a day... or an instant!
Don't tell me now - I don't want to know when the next shooting star will come...
('Cause I'm alive right here, in this moment!)
Don't tell me now - even if this will be my last time, I don't want to regret it...
(Y'know, you and I are here together!)
The wind begins to blow without warning.
People's voices can be heard - anger is amid their prayers;
Their pain is quietly reborn when they look upon those scars.
After hearing that song so many times, over and over again...
(Can you hear my voice?)
... even if that distant city- your distant dreams- were to be lost, I'm sure you could still sing that melody you once loved!
Don't let me down - I know you too well, so don't try to deceive me...
(Hey, you can hear it too, can't you?)
Don't let me down - I have a melody I want to play out, even if it puts my life at risk...
(Hey, you already know what I mean, right?)
The wind is blowing.
Don't let me down tonight...
We'll find that constellation!
Don't tell me now - I don't want to know when the next shooting star will come...
('Cause I'm alive right here, in this moment.)
Don't tell me now - even if this will be my last time, I don't want to regret it...
(Y'know, you and I are here together.)
The wind begins to blow without warning.
Don't tell me now　Don't tell me now
Don't tell me now
Don't let me down　Don't let me down
Don't let me down
Don't tell me now　Don't tell me now
Don't tell me now
Don't let me down　Don't let me down
Don't let me down
Don't tell me now　Don't tell me now
Don't let me down　Don't let me down
AXIA ~ ダイスキでダイキライ
AXIA ~ Daisuki de Daikirai
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
That smile of yours I just saw... may be the last I ever see;
Even watching you talk with someone else would be a cherished second.
In this world where our lives hold less weight than a feather,
We managed to meet... because you were the meaning of my life!
This pain is the AXIA of my heart!
You soar through a one-way sky, with a slight fever,
Becoming a merciless rainbow that fades instantly;
Seeing you so far off, I love... and hate you.
Born into this world alone... we'll all end up dying alone...
But nonetheless, we can't live alone - our frequencies yearn for one another!
Our feeling of love permeate our throbbing wounds,
Filling them with that one phrase we can never manage to say.
Even amid tears, this AXIA will illuminate tomorrow!
Our heartbeats are connected by ephemeral particles...
Like a dream suspended in a haze of heat,
We came to know of eternal days: a cold-hearted passion.
Even if my day of rest comes as I ride along in this vessel of time,
That ray of light, holding feelings for one and only... will never die out!
I'll never remember you again-
Because I've never forgotten you, even once!
This pain is the AXIA of my heart!
You soar through a one-way sky, with a slight fever,
Stealing my love away - it's enough to leave me in despair;
Even if this love remains unfulfilled (even if we're far apart), I love... and hate you.
I love... and hate you...
GIRAFFE BLUES
Ginbei - Macross Wiki
I'm unable to catch up to you;
What were you always watching from this place?
Counting the things you'd lost, despite what you'd gained,
You were even trying to hide your tears, weren't you?
Those eyes that looked too faithfully forward,
Were seeing this world from a slanted angle...
Dreams cannot be drawn by you alone;
An unseen wind carries them on their way.
If you get the feeling you can fly high and far,
Never let go of this hand holding you firmly.
The truths within your heart,
Can't be communicated with words alone.
Even if you claim them as your own, that unfading void,
Is only being covered up with a smile.
Before you knew it, you'd gotten too close -
Unable to hear my song as you once did.
Where are you now, my beloved,
In this world that's lost all color... all meaning?
I still believe we can fly high and far,
But amid that unseen sky, our wings are shred to pieces.
Dreams cannot be drawn by you alone;
An unseen wind carries them on their way.
If you get the feeling you can fly high and far,
Never let go of this hand holding you firmly.
(Your dream...)
(... by an unseen wind)
I know your blues.
オーラ・サーラ～光る風
Ōra Sāra ~ Hikarukaze
Song of the Wind
(ft Melody Chubak)
ザルド・ヴァーサ!～決意の風
Zarudo vu~āsa!~ Ketsui no kaze
Wind of Determination
(ft Melody Chubak)
ルーチェット・アルカーン～星の歌
Rūchetto arukān ~-boshi no uta
Star Song
(ft Ami Koshimizu)
MC3
涙目爆発音
Namidame Bakuhatsuon
(ft Yoko Hikasa)
Winterbells1 - Macross Wiki
The more I lightly touch it
with these fingers I reach out
The more I'll let it blast in hot
The explosive sound of teary eyes
(The teary eyes Hah)
Why can't we reach there?
Where in the world is the future?
All the faint afterimages
Ah I've torn them off
I aim for a bright day
This cycle of death & rebirth is so vexing that I need to grind my teeth
Nothing would be change
It's unsolved
YES NO(YES NO)
I ask a question to my heart
Do you still have some power left
to keep moving forward?
Ah I'm sorry (I'm sorry)
Ah I'm sorry...
I almost ended up answering it with NO, but
Just cry!
The more I lightly touch it
with these fingers I reach out
The more I want to grasp it,
even to the end of universe
The faster my heart beats
that it almost bursts out
The more I'll let it blast in hot
The explosive sound of teary eyes
Keep running and then scattering
The balls of our spirit
are wandering through the night sky
Just like a sudden comet shower
YES NO(YES NO)
I always make it sure
Where in the world is my true place?
Ah I'm sorry (I'm sorry)
Ah I'm sorry...
Now, I still don't know
But please let me answer it with YES
Just cry!
The wilder my pulse and my blood circulating within my body
The more I can't stop it even if it's ended in the Galaxy
The faster my heart beats that it almost bursts out
The more I'll let it blast in hot
The explosive sound of teary eyes
I'll always try to stand up over and over again
Even when I almost burst into cry,
With you, I'll take your hand and be reborn
Reincarnate to myself that will bloom in tomorrow
The more I lightly touch it
with these fingers I reach out
The more I want to grasp it,
even to the end of universe
The faster my heart beats
that it almost bursts out
The more I'll let it blast in hot
The explosive sound of teary eyes
Just cry!
僕らの戦場
Bokura no Senjō
Our Battlefield
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
If you've managed to glimpse that blip in the sky...
If you've managed to hear my shaking voice...
Fly up, high enough to be ripped to pieces,
Upon the eternal wings of torn memories!
The things we talked about that day...
The things we could always laugh about together...
Until the day those times can be revived, our only choice is to take a stand!
Break it apart, and feel me more and more!
Are you there, there amid it all?
Ahh, lives blooming upon the battlefield: Burn on! Burn on!
If by killing, we're destined to perish anyway,
Seethe, seethe onward to the ends of destruction!
Awaken a miracle - on our way to that closed off sky!
Amidst innumerable sensations flying about,
You'll risk losing even your truest self.
Under the concentrated fire of unseen doubts,
The only way to victory is having the strength to admit you're weak.
If you hadn't been you...
And I hadn't been me...
We'd have never come to know this feeling!
Cut through, closer and closer to the dark side of justice!
Run on, run on - until you're reduced to ash
Abandon all reason and let out a roar from your heart!
Sever those ties; if you can eventually be there with me,
In the new galaxy that will be born,
Our brilliance could become unrivaled!
Everyone is trying to survive following the lead of others,
Knowing not the reason for their frustrations.
But rather than living on as if we we're already dead,
We'll let our red blood flow... and bear our fangs -
That's our proof that we're truly alive!
Break it apart, and feel me more and more!
Are you there, there amid it all?
Ahh, lives blooming upon the battlefield: Burn on! Burn on!
If by killing, we're destined to perish anyway,
Seethe, seethe onward to the ends of destruction!
Awaken a miracle - on our way to that closed off sky!
Walkure Attack!
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
'tis, 'tis feel LOVE　'tis, 'tis feel LOVE
If we don't get flyin', we won't be able to see the future,
So take me to the farthest reaches -
Fly away!
When you reach out your hand to save someone,
I want you to choose me... Ah!
'tis, 'tis feel LOVE
(I'm feeling so excited!)
I bet you can hear those vibrations of life:
(Ah, feeling Star! Wow!)
By tomorrow, surely...
This new world will begin!
Pray for love,
(fly to the sky)
As this melody plays out;
It continues into the distance - all the way to our blue planet!
Speak of dreams,
(into the dream)
Just don't fade away, shooting love!
Come on and take off -
Just flap those wings!
A lonely future...
(So fly)
I won't give it to anyone!
(No cry)
So guide me by that hand... to the farthest reaches of Hell!
Scatter that karma living deep in your eyes,
And release your trapped heart -
Fly away!
The scenery of that day when I was all alone,
Looks so beautiful when we're together... Ah!
'tis, 'tis feel LOVE
(It's shining so brightly!)
I bet we have at least enough power,
(Ah, feeling Star! Wow!)
I'm sure there is power to protect
Grip this hand,
(fly to the sky)
As these symphonies overlap;
We're believing that our blue planet can someday be healed!
Please don't tell me,
(into the dream)
That we'll never meet again, shooting love!
Ah, break out now -
And put up a fight!
Listen to this scream;
Until this path,
Loses its flame,
I'm gonna keep it burning bright!
Don't forget,
'Cause I never will!
So once more...
As many times as it takes...
We're not done here yet!
'tis, 'tis feel LOVE　'tis, 'tis feel LOVE
I believe we'll be able to smile in the end,
(Ah, feeling Star! Wow!)
I'm sure that tomorrow I'll change the world!
Pray for love, As this melody plays out;
It continues into the distance - all the way to our blue planet!
Speak of dreams,
(into the dream)
Never ceasing your tale, shooting love!
Come on and take off!
Take off!
Take oath to eternity -
(Fly to the sky)
This last stage granted to us;
Our blue planet will illuminate everything there!
I won't let you tell me,
(into the dream)
That we'll never meet again, shooting love!
Ah, break out now -
And put up a fight!
I won't give anyone,
(So fly)
A lonely future,
(No cry)
So guide me by that hand... to the farthest reaches of Hell!
破滅の純情
Hametsu no junjō
Destructive Purity
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
I'm standing upon the burning wreckage,
Though I've forgotten why, or how long I've been here...
Amid these flames that choke my breath,
No matter what I search for, or manage to find - it's all quite pointless!
So break, and overcome... the ecstasy of our past;
Even if it's the worst possible outcome, we've gotta choose the future!
I'm gonna go.
Reaching the limits of love forever,
If we can sing until we're writhing in agony,
Our souls will coil into an ouroboros! Yeah!
If we can still manage to scream then,
Seething with life abound,
What lies beyond will be a destructive purity!
A madness blowing through flows within my chest,
Though I don't know for how long, or why...
Amidst speed so intense I can't even blink,
To cry out, or expressing my woes, just seems so futile!
Roar aloud- Burst out- our collective emotion!
Even amid the worst reality, we have to choose ourselves!
I'm gonna fly.
To the slimmest margin of love forever,
If we can dance to the point of madness,
Our souls will reach the critical point! Yeah!
If we can still manage to move then,
Reaching that shining sky,
What lies beyond will be a destructive purity!
That purity!
That purity!!
That purity!!!
That purity!!!!
That purity!!!!!
Attain enlightenment, then starve - on to the next survival;
If you're devoted to protecting something, proceed onward through Hell!
"I love you."
Reaching yet another Last Game Over,
If we can lose everything again,
Our souls will sever their ties to chaos! Yeah!
If we can manage to return to the day we were born,
And rest among those days departed,
What lies beyond will be waves of slightly feverish emotions!
Reaching the limits of love forever,
If we can sing until we're writhing in agony,
Our souls will bloom a cycle of life and death! Yeah!
If we can still manage to scream then,
Seething with life abound,
What lies beyond will be a destructive purity!
Ah,
Everyone's a baby:
But I'll still forgive you - a climactic chaos!
絶対零度θノヴァティック
Zettai Reido Th Novu~atikku
Absolute zero degree θ Novatic
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
Flying!  With a kiss (a kiss)
Of love (of love),
I'll link to the furthest reaches!
I love you!
I pierce onward through this passion...
My absolute zero with you! (Hah~)
I'll raise the spark of a dream within you,
Embracing everything you believe in:
A truly reckless gene!
The more you value that existence, the heat in your chest will seem unreal -
Just shake off your concerns and squeeze me into another dimension!
Crushed tight, I love us just as we are... (Gaze upon me)
... born from this colliding core!
All the tears, and fates, we can't experience alone... connect with one another!
Flying!  Living (entranced) at the (speed) of love,
We're super novatic!
We can do it!
Even if I end up covered in scars - I don't mind, as long as we're together!
By your pure heart, (Charm me)... send your wish (to the sky):
A hyper big bang deep breath genesis!
Expending our lives, we achieve fusion:
My absolute zero with you! (Hah~)
The first cry of an incubated promise rings out;
A story that won't end without a fight!
The weakness to never give up is a mythical polyhedron;
It'll be alright, so jump into this reunion!
Electrifying, linked activity- (Reaction)
Feeling it out requires every part of our bodies...
I want this to come true, no matter what... you'll become my dream!
Send it out!
Letting love (take the lead), just dance (you're free!): An illusionary aquarium!
I can make it there!
When you open your eyes, I'll be by your side, never letting go again!
Your devoted (Eyes) will grow stormy (like a squall):
An instinctual RUSH phantom ON legacy!
This silence is an eternal pause:
A vacuum of vibrasion!
Lay bare...
(What is life? What is my life for you?)
... that unexplored wish! A star of resolution!
With a kiss of love, I'll link to the furthest reaches!
I love you!
The warmth of our touching cheeks can't be brushed away.
Having taken captured your passage now,
I release a forbidden splash resonance, (Hah~ Tightly)
As it pierces my heart!
Flying!
Living (entranced) at the (speed) of love,
We're super novatic!
We can do it!
Even if I end up covered in scars - I don't mind, as long as we're together!
By your pure heart, (Charm me)... send your wish (to the sky):
A hyper big bang deep breath genesis!
Expending our lives, we achieve fusion:
My absolute zero with you! (Hah~)
MC4
一度だけの恋なら
Ichidodake no Koinara
If You are in Love Only Once
Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
If this love can only come once, Let’s have some fun inside of you:
Let’s share an indulgent kiss!
The petals of this flower, dancing through the air…
The starry skies I’ve yet to finish counting…
Even if I fight back the tears, saying everything is your fault,
I can’t tell anyone about this fluttering in my chest!
(Send it out…) Until it breaks-
(Send it out…) Until it takes flight:
(Until the end…) Delivering the prayer-
(…of time) Bound within my heart!
Following my feelings- following what I believe in- I’ll send everything flying free:
Soar! Soar! Soar!
If this love can only come once, let’s have some fun inside of you:
Let’s share a kiss that’s faster than light, just wait!
That body you’ve nearly forgotten… the heartbeat you can hear aloud…
Go beyond all the things that limit this dream!
C’mon and steal me away- get up close, just as you are!
By the time lightning sears the night sky,
My passion will be catching aflame!
I'll be made aware that my mind and body are one,
With an uneasiness I can't put to words...
The two of us... found one another
The two of us... searched together
For the shining light of your life
Blooming in the space of darkness.
While about to burst, while flashing bright, shoot right through my heart:
Bang! Bang! Bang!
Within your dream, let's dance with a violent passion that will never come again:
Give me an embrace wider than the expanse of space, hold me oh so tight!
Rather than putting on a show of strength... rather than bonds consisting only of words...
Commit yourself to living through each moment together!
C’mon and take my freedom, tie me up, 'cause we're not done yet!
Don't let go of that ripened impulse;
Come and catch me,
Faster than you've ever gone before!
If this love can only come once, let’s have some fun inside of you:
Let’s share a kiss that’s faster than light, just wait!
That body you’ve nearly forgotten… the heartbeat you can hear aloud…
Go beyond all the things that limit this dream!
C’mon and steal me away, get up close
Within your dream, let's dance with a violent passion that will never come again:
Give me an embrace wider than the expanse of space - hold me oh so tight!
Rather than putting on a show of strength... rather than bonds consisting only of words...
Commit yourself to living through each moment together!
C’mon and take my freedom- tie me up- 'cause we're not done yet!
MC5
MC6
ワルキューレがとまらない
Walküre  ga tomaranai
Walküre does not stop
Winterbells1 - Macross Wiki
Walküre can't be stopped (Fu Fu Fu)
Walküre won't stop (Fu Fu Fu)
ROCKIN' MY JET
COSMIC LOVE…　 TAKE OFF!
Ah…　Please tell me In the corner of endless memories,
Fallen tears will be turn into stars, right?
Ah…　Let me hear The lullaby of painful sighs
Those day sky has engraved you into my mind
My heart is dancing
Suddenly, when my body starts to sing
Something overflows within my heart is ―Passion―
It can't be stopped!
Hold me just like this, until I wake up from this dream
I need nothing I even don't need love
because I'll be broken because of it Ah
I don't mind to get naked, watch over me until morning comes
I'm so desperate Forget them all
This affection can't be stopped
Walküre can't be stopped (Fu Fu Fu)
Walküre won't stop (Fu Fu Fu)
ROCKIN' MY JET
COSMIC LOVE…　 TAKE OFF!
Ah…　Answer me Within the boundary of sucked fever,
an upset breath will become a wind, right?
Ah…　Please fool around Paper moon floated in the darkness of night
will tell you a tale that nobody can talk about
It's strange, once my heart beat resounds my gaze become hot
The song we will play is ―Lamentation―
It can't be stopped!
Pierce me through just like this, until my breath stops
Wallowed in night, smeared with lies
I just want to be broken Ah
I don't mind if you finish me off I've been ready for it
Being flustered is a really fatal wound
I can't stop feeling uneasy
(Ha- flower is flower)
Falling lightly Love will be forgiven by love
Swaying around Sins will be mingled with sins
(So ephmeral, that is...) (blooming so beautiful and wilted Ha)
O the melody of mischievous love Open your eyes
Now, I will shine be burning in love showing the true way
Ah-　to those fellow travelers Ah-　the resonance of fright
Hey, right now!
Please hurt me just like this, Do it... in trance?
Sky is burning Stars are burning I almost falling in love with you
It can't be stopped!
Hold me just like this, until I wake up from this dream
I need nothing I even don't need love because
I'll be broken because of it Ah
I don't mind to get naked, watch over me until morning comes
I'm so desperate Forget them all This affection.....
....can't be stopped!
Pierce me through just like this, until my breath stops
Wallowed in night, smeared with lies
I just want to be broken Ah
I don't mind if you finish me off I've been ready for it
Being flustered is a really fatal wound
I can't stop feeling uneasy
Walküre can't be stopped (Fu Fu Fu)
Walküre won't stop (Fu Fu Fu)
ROCKIN' MY JET
COSMIC LOVE…　 TAKE OFF!
Walküre can't be stopped (Fu Fu Fu)
Walküre won't stop (Fu Fu Fu)
ROCKIN' MY JET
COSMIC LOVE…　 TAKE OFF!
MC7
愛・おぼえていますか
Ai oboete imasu ka
Do you Remember Love?
Shira - YouTube
Sha la la la, do you remember?
I love you, so remember
Right now, I hear your voice
Saying "Come here to me"
Just when it seemed loneliness had beaten me.
Right now, I see you walking over to me
I close my eyes and wait for you to come.
Till yesterday, it seemed filled only with tears
But now my heart is...
Do you remember?  The time when our eyes first met?
Do you remember? The time when our hands first touched?
That was the very first time I set out on the journey of love.
I love you, so
Sha la la la, do you remember?
I love you, so remember
Right now, I can feel your gaze, though you're not here with me
And in my body a warmth begins to glow
Right now, I believe in your love, so won't you please...
Watch over me from so far away?
Till yesterday, it seemed filled only with tears
Now the world is...
Do you remember? The time when our eyes first met?
Do you remember? The time when our hands first touched?
That was the very first time I set out on the journey of love.
I love you, so
I'm not alone anymore
Now that you're here with me
Do you remember? The time when our eyes first met?
Do you remember? The time when our hands first touched?
That was the very first time I set out on the journey of love.
I love you, so
I'm not alone anymore
Now that you're here with me
恋！ ハレイション THE WAR
Koi! Halation THE WAR
Love! Halation THE WAR
Winterbells1 - Macross Wiki
Welcome to Walküre World
Welcome!
My heart… feels your love
Welcome to Walküre World
Screaming in a passion, there’s no more slowing down!
“SOS!” blares the siren
Love is halation and war!
Everything begins when I awaken in the morning light
(My own story)
It feels somehow a little different from always
I’m rubbing at my eyes
Cleared for takeoff, three two
And one-piece dress fluttering in the wind
It’s turning on my supersonic drive
When we collide, a galactic
boom comes from our hearts, and deculture!
Starboard thrusters away, I’m gonna light you up!
Diving on an impulse, there’s no more turning back!
“SOS!” goes the signal blaze
Love is changing the world!
All the colours whirling like a kaleidoscope
And the typhoon of my feelings has swept me away
Screaming in a passion, there’s no more slowing down!
Love, love, melody of love!
Now the stars in the heavens whisper to us in glowing lights
I hear their voices saying “feel your love”
My life used to be a repeat but now every day is dazzlingly new
And I’ve become beautiful too
Our chances are galactic
You run into me, and deculture!
Hard to port, there’s a fire that’s burning me up!
Floundering but flying, no more just a fantasy!
“SOS!” goes the changing panorama
Love is shaking the wind!
Now this is like a cosmic wonderland
Even the ordinary things we do
(Shine with a prismatic radiant glow)
Who knew just your being in this world
Could set my heart dancing for joy
A joy that’s all for you…
Screaming in a passion, there’s no more slowing down!
“SOS!” sings my love for you
It’s halation and war!
Surely there’ll be more
More please, hold me tight
Tightly through the night
Night and day I’m sure
Surely there’ll be more (more please)
More please, hold me tight (tightly)
Tightly through the night (all night)
Night and day I’m sure
Surely there’ll be more
More please, hold me tight
Tightly through the night
When I’m with you, I feel connected through and through…!
Welcome to Walküre World
MC8
ルンがピカッと光ったら
Rune ga Pika tto Hikattara
When My Rune Sparkles
Series Subtitles / Whitbyfish - Macross Wiki
You ready for this?
I heard a rumor that the world's gonna end someday
C'mon tell me something I don't know
Looking up at the sky once, I felt the future happening here and now
I was totally in sync with your wind
I've found a place where I can still be a girl
So I gotta do it, There's no stopping now!
It's coming right atcha!
When my rune shines bright
Wow woh wow woh
I'm gonna fall in love
Pariru Pa-rira, It's all your fault
Parira Rune Pika That I'm invincible
Someone's out there suffering, but you say it's too painful to join the fight
That's no good, we can't move forward like that!
At that moment, the sky wavered from the trail you drew through the sky,
Giving me the courage to sing!
Just living life seems to leave me with no time left,
So I can't afford to back down from this feeling!
Rune-Shiny Beam!
When my rune shines bright
Wow woh wow woh
You'll be able to fly high!
Tariru taarira, my love...
Tarira, with my rune shining ...it's unlimited!
When my rune shines bright
Wow woh wow woh
The whole world will fall in love!
Pariru paarira, feel the wind,
huh huh
Parira, with those runes alight, keep shining bright!
No matter what happens, my love...
huh huh
No matter how things end up - ... will be unstoppable!
Hardheaded Attack!